biz-logo.com 2001-08-07

# Disclaimer & Privacy Policy

**BizLOGO** creates a high resolution graphics format for your design. The logo may be submitted for printing. However, it is up to your printer to properly setup the print process for the logo. BizLOGO assumes no responsibility of any nature for color variations, graphics distortions or other variables associated with the printing of your logo or in the graphics display of your logo. Display colors vary with both ink in printing and graphics display adapters for internet publications. 

Any and all claims against or involving BizLOGO are limited to the amount paid and must be brought in Detroit, Michigan. Therefore, all damages whether consequential or otherwise are specifically excluded, except for refund of any money paid to BizLOGO. All work done is deemed for commercial purposes.

In the event of non-payment you hereby agree that the Courts of Michigan shall have full authority to grant judgement for any unpaid balances, along with reasonable attorneys fees and cost.

BizLOGO may have, from time to time display banners linking other sites. BizLOGO assumes no responsibility for the referring site. They are separate legal entities with no affiliation with BizLOGO.

BizLOGO reserves the right to display your graphics design without compensation to you so others can see the quality of work we do. If you do not wish us to display your design then you must notify us and we will comply with your business instructions.   

## **OUR POLICY ON DISCLOSURE:**

**BizLOGO** is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. We believe that your confidence in BizLOGO and our practices insures our growth as a business. We follow a strict policy of professional integrity and responsibility to our visitors and clients.

The following information is our policy of how your personal information will be treated. BizLOGO reserves the right to change it's policies at any time, so please check back periodically for updated information.

BizLOGO collects information based upon information that you provide in order to give you the products and services you seek. You should be aware BizLOGO's Internet access partners, advertisers, and web sites that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those Internet access partners, advertisers, and web sites linked to BizLOGO are not covered by this privacy statement, nor are we responsible for their policies and/or practices. By clicking on a banner you acknowledge that certain information about you may be collected. Occasionally, opportunities may arise that we believe our visitors and clients would be interested in. In such event this information may be supplied to those companies, unless you notify us otherwise. You may email us with instructions to remove you from any e-mail and promotions list that we maintain.

Document Last Modified 01/31/2020 12:49:10 

### [Return to HOME Page](http://www.biz-logo.com/index.html)
**BizLOGO** creates a high resolution graphics format for your design. The logo may be submitted for printing. However, it is up to your printer to properly setup the print process for the logo. BizLOGO assumes no responsibility of any nature for color variations, graphics distortions or other variables associated with the printing of your logo or in the graphics display of your logo. Display colors vary with both ink in printing and graphics display adapters for internet publications. 

Any and all claims against or involving BizLOGO are limited to the amount paid and must be brought in Detroit, Michigan. Therefore, all damages whether consequential or otherwise are specifically excluded, except for refund of any money paid to BizLOGO. All work done is deemed for commercial purposes.

In the event of non-payment you hereby agree that the Courts of Michigan shall have full authority to grant judgement for any unpaid balances, along with reasonable attorneys fees and cost.

BizLOGO may have, from time to time display banners linking other sites. BizLOGO assumes no responsibility for the referring site. They are separate legal entities with no affiliation with BizLOGO.

BizLOGO reserves the right to display your graphics design without compensation to you so others can see the quality of work we do. If you do not wish us to display your design then you must notify us and we will comply with your business instructions.   

## **OUR POLICY ON DISCLOSURE:**

**BizLOGO** is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. We believe that your confidence in BizLOGO and our practices insures our growth as a business. We follow a strict policy of professional integrity and responsibility to our visitors and clients.

The following information is our policy of how your personal information will be treated. BizLOGO reserves the right to change it's policies at any time, so please check back periodically for updated information.

BizLOGO collects information based upon information that you provide in order to give you the products and services you seek. You should be aware BizLOGO's Internet access partners, advertisers, and web sites that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those Internet access partners, advertisers, and web sites linked to BizLOGO are not covered by this privacy statement, nor are we responsible for their policies and/or practices. By clicking on a banner you acknowledge that certain information about you may be collected. Occasionally, opportunities may arise that we believe our visitors and clients would be interested in. In such event this information may be supplied to those companies, unless you notify us otherwise. You may email us with instructions to remove you from any e-mail and promotions list that we maintain.

Document Last Modified 01/31/2020 12:49:11 

### [Return to HOME Page](http://www.biz-logo.com/index.html)
